I’ve never made like a big dick line in
any of my songs.
That was my first one.
‘Cause like I’m not on some like micro
shit.
You know what I mean?
But like I’m also like not crazy…
You know what I’m saying?
But I was so worried that the girls I used to
mess with were gonna be like...
“Song’s hard."
"But just know like…"
"It ain’t that big.”
Nobody said nothing so we’re in the clear.
Maybe they’re like, “It was…”
Like maybe they think I’m telling the truth.
I don’t know.
Next line bruh.
Clipse.
‘Hell Hath No Fury.’
“We Got It For Cheap.”
It’s the intro.
We had been listening to Clipse all week.
Me and my producer, 2forwOyNE.
And I played him that one.
As soon as we got to the studio, that was
the immediate influence.
Everybody been noticing that, saying, “Oh
this sounds just like ‘We Got It For Cheap.’”
Definitely.
It’s totally paying homage.
Let me start off by saying, what’s crazy
about this record is all growing up, I was
never into drugs or drinking.
All through high school.
I didn’t do it.
I just wasn’t that intrigued.
And then I remember, the summer after I graduated,
a big group of my friends were doing that
and it was the first thing that ever made
me like, “Dang."
"I wanna do that.”
So one night, I just did it with them and
this is before I smoked or drank ever.
It’s like the first drug I ever did.
It was a trip for sure.
I was feeling fly that day.
Not everyday you feel fly but that day I was
feeling like, “I feel like a pimp.”
Like I just feel like I was on some cool shit.
Everybody in Louisville likes Big Red, likes
Grippos.
It’s like a signature soda from where we’re
from.
A lot of people have never ever heard of the
drink but to us, it might as well be a Pepsi.
You know what I mean?
It’s a major soda.
Private Garden, the collective.
A lot of
fellas like we ain’t even got cars so a
lot of the guys can’t get around.
Can’t get to work.
We want whips though.
We want big whips.
That’s what we want.
We want everybody to be able to drive.
If you trying to grip grain, you gotta get
breaded.
I don’t even really step out to the pool
or anything ‘cause it’s not really worth
it for me.
Things go left quick.
I just get burnt bro.
And my man over here, Urban, he gets tan.
Like nice tan.
And he’s like a little more cut than me
too, so we step out and this dude just looks
like Hercules.
And I look okay, like don’t get me wrong,
I look alright.
I be getting burnt.
The back of my neck, my arms and shit.
I’ve been getting burnt my whole life so
it’s terrible.
My whole life I’ve been blushing.
Like without realizing it sometimes.
This dude will tell me, “You’re blushing
right now.”
I’m like, “Bro I feel good."
"Why am I blushing?”
Sometimes, I’ll blush when I get embarrassed.
I used to get embarrassed when I was younger.
My boy used to make it worse, my friend Copeland.
Anytime it would happen, he would just look
at me, like maybe I’d be talking to a girl
or something, he’d be like, “Ready Freddy?”
He’d just say that every time.
“Ready Freddy?”
And that shit made it worse ‘cause once
you realize you’re doing it, then you’re
just like, “Aw.”
Half this interviews been about redness on
my skin.
We gotta get past this.